<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="news1_title">U-Report Reaches 1 Million Registered Users Worldwide</string>
    <string name="news1_content">
        Today 1 million people from 15 countries across the world joined hands to become agents of social change in their communities. These 1 million people stepped forward to no longer be passive recipients of social services but become active participants in the national and global development process.\n\n
        Now their voices can be heard and they can influence change at the national and international level using U-Report.
    </string>
    <drawable name="news1_cover">@drawable/news1_cover_image</drawable>
    <string name="news1_author">U-report Global</string>
    <string name="news1_category">General</string>

    <string name="news2_title">Swaziland Scouts Taking U-Report Platform To Communities</string>
    <string name="news2_content">
        Swaziland Scouts in partnership with UNICEF Swaziland are rolling out U-Report, a free SMS platform for youth and community participation designed to address issues that matter to you and your community.\n\n
        Swazi Scouts are getting ready to take U-Report down to communities which will help communities to report on anything that is affecting them, be it crime, health issues and also promote youth interaction.
    </string>
    <drawable name="news2_cover">@drawable/news2_cover_image</drawable>
    <string name="news2_author">Scouts</string>
    <string name="news2_category">Social Policy</string>

    <string name="news3_title">U-Report is now live in Africa\'s largest country</string>
    <string name="news3_content">
        U-Report Nigeria’s launch was hosted by renowned MC, TV and radio talk show host, Toke Makinwa.\n\n
        Makinwa moderated an interactive session with some of the National Youth Corp members who were in attendance sharing their experiences so far on the U-Report platform.\n\n

        UNICEF Nigeria Representative Jean Gough gave the opening remarks to officially start off the Launch:\n\n

        "U-Report is a platform for youths most especially because it gives them an avenue to express their opinion."

        "It is the youth in communities that are driving this agenda"

        A dance crew led by Kaffy, thrilled the guests to a spectacular show. Goodwill messages from representatives of National Youth Service Corps (NYSC), United Nation Development Programme (UNDP) and National Primary Healthcare Development Agency (NPHCDA) were also shared. James Powell, U-Report Global Strategist and Coordinator also sent in a goodwill video message from the Global Innovation Centre congratulating U-Report Nigeria on its official launch.
    </string>
    <drawable name="news3_cover">@drawable/news3_cover_image</drawable>
    <string name="news3_author">Scouts</string>
    <string name="news3_category">General</string>

</resources>