<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="story1_title">I have no idea what to do with my life: Is that a crime?</string>
    <string name="story1_content">
        Today, many teenagers are constantly bombarded with a tough question: \"what career do you want to pursue?\" Or \"what do you want to do in future?\" These two questions are asked by many adults, who are surprised when they are met by deafening silence.\n\n
        Being a teenager myself, I am 15, and have two more years to go before I complete high school, I have come across many people who have asked me this question. Since I don\'t have the slightest clue of what career path I want to take, I would be frank and reply, \"I don\'t know\".\n\n
        It did not take me long to notice that the questioner\'s smile would quickly disappear, while their eyes would clearly show their disappointment as they graciously reassured me with pity in their voices that, \"You are still young\" and \"You still have time to decide\".\n\n
        After going through countless scenes like this one, I finally decided to shorten my three-word answers to one word: \"Medicine\", never mind that I still have no idea what I want to do with my life after high school. I am just tired of the disappointed and pitiful glances that come my way whenever I tell the truth. If anything, their reaction makes me feel as if not knowing is a sin.\n\n
        No doubt, there are many young people who are faced with the same predicament as me. They don\'t really know how to answer this question. What\'s worse is that some of us know exactly how to answer this probing question but lie, because we know that the truth will be unpalatable. For example; I have a friend who tell those who ask that she wants to become an accountant, when the reality is that she wants to study art and design, where her passion and talent lies. But art and design is still not considered a \'real\' career in our society, and to avoid ridicule, she lies.\n\n
        In the school I go to, a biology, chemistry or physics class is three times as large as the music class. This is not because fewer students are interested in music but because society says it is more respectable to be an engineer than a musician.\n\n
        Superior\n\n
        But why is this? Why are you considered more successful if you an engineer, and not taken seriously if you say you are a musician ? Or artist? If I am talented in singing or playing a musical instrument, why shouldn\'t I pursue music?\n\n
        Can someone please explain to me why some careers are considered \"superior\" and others \'inferior\" ? Does it have something to do with income? I don\'t think so because there must be artists who earn more than engineers. Does it have something to do with popularity then? I doubt it, because I know musicians who are more popular than lawyers. Is it for the honor and respect? Well, I think not because I know athletes who are more respected than doctors.\n\n

        Same lenses\n\n
        I am not implying that some careers are better that others. All I am trying to say is that each of these careers should be viewed through the same lenses because they all have the possibility of being fulfilling - if you are passionate about something, you are likely to succeed at it.\n\n
        So, if I wake up one day and decide to become a designer like the famous Luis Vuitton, nobody is going to stop me. Before I conclude, I would like to ask one last question. What is wrong with me not knowing what career path I want to take? There is nothing wrong at all; one day, I am going to figure it out, and when I do, I will give it my all, and become a name to reckon with in that profession.
    </string>

    <string name="story2_title">No water in my region</string>
    <string name="story2_content">
        Despite a narrowing disparity in access to cleaner water and better sanitation between rural and urban areas, sharp inequalities still persist around the world.

        Poor sanitation and contaminated water are linked to transmission of diseases such as cholera, diarrhoea, dysentery, hepatitis A, and typhoid. In addition, inadequate or absent water and sanitation services in health care facilities put already vulnerable patients at additional risk of infection and disease.
    </string>

    <string name="story3_title">Education issues</string>
    <string name="story3_content">
        In many countries around the world, significantly less public resources are used to educate children in the poorest 20 per cent of society than their counterparts in the most affluent 20 per cent, according to a new report issued today by UNICEF. This difference can be as much as 18 times.
    </string>

    <string name="story4_title">Politics story</string>
    <string name="story4_content">
        The government should provide a good administration for countries, cities and villages. I disagree with a lot of things in my country. What do you think about? Contribute with this story nooooow!
    </string>

</resources>